stoppayingcablebills.com 2014-07-09

# Online TV | Free TV, Movies & Sports in your Browser

An Easy & Free Extension for TV Lovers!

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [info@stoppayingcablebills.com](mailto:%20info@stoppayingcablebills.com)

At stoppayingcablebills.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by This website and how it is used. 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, this website makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons 

This website does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## Information Collected

The information collected may be used to send the user information about our company, company product releases and online products related to the entertainment niche.

Your information will NOT be shared with any third parties. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; to opt out send an email to [info@stoppayingcablebills.com](mailto:%20info@stoppayingcablebills.com) with “Opt Out” in the subject line. Or Simply click on the unsubscribe link available at the bottom of all our newsletters.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on This website.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to This website and other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Widget Bucks
  * Adbrite
  * Clickbank
  * Azoogle
  * Chitika
  * Linkshare
  * Amazon
  * Kontera

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on This website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

This website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. For more information about our privacy policy feel free to contact us by email at [info@stoppayingcablebills.com](mailto:%20info@stoppayingcablebills.com)

If you believe that our website has collected incorrect information or if you would like to dispute any information, please also contact us at the following email address [info@stoppayingcablebills.com](mailto:%20info@stoppayingcablebills.com)

## Affiliates

We have alot of affiliates around the globe there promote this service and they do their marketing too

The Television Toolbar is powered by Conduit Ltd

Stoppayingcablebills.com allows users to download a Toolbar which is powered by Conduit. Any third party products, brands or trademarks listed above are the sole property of their respective owner. No affiliation or endorsement is intended or implied.

You can remove/uninstall the toolbar at any given time. To learn more about how to uninstall/remove the toolbar please visit our Uninstall page of click here

Learn more about Conduit's services by visiting the following link <http://www.conduit.com/>
